{
    "question": ": I ... visit my grandmother house\r\n will\r\n can\r\n could\r\n shall\r\n would",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>I <strong>would</strong><strong> </strong>visit my grandmother house</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "i-am-can-fly-639",
            "question": "I am........ can fly\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bird</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>.................. </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Mine Craft  creative mode</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "look-at-the-body-of-the-latter-can-you-find-the-following-items-957",
            "question": "Look at the body of the latter. can you find the following items    a. the date\r\nb. the time\r\nc. the contact for RSV\r\nd. the dress code\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D.Thw dress code</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-text-is-for-question-numbers-14-17-my-neighbour-mr-and-mrs-937",
            "question": "This text is for question numbers 14-17    My Neighbour\r\nMr. And Mrs. Ruslan are my neighbors. They have two children,\r\na son and a daughter. Their names are Fahril and Mayada. Mr. Ruslan is a lecturer in\r\na state university in our town. Mrs. Ruslanis a house wife. She likes cooking many kinds\r\nof food. She often invites me to cook together in her kitchen. Mr. Ruslan's family has some\r\npets. There are some birds, a cat and two rabits. I sometimes feed them. I like guing there\r\nbecause they are kind and friendly. They always show good attitude to everyone.\r\n14. Does Ruslan's family live far from the writer's house?\r\na. Yes, they do\r\nc. Yes, it does\r\nb. No, they do not\r\nd. No, it doesn't\r\n15. Where does Mr. Ruslan work? He works in a.....\r\na. University\r\nc. kitchen\r\nb. school\r\nd. company\r\n16. I sometimes feed them. The underlined word means.......\r\na. ask food to somebody or something\r\nb.give food to somebody or something\r\nC. eat food with somebody\r\nd. take food froom somebody\r\n17. \" she ofteninvites me to cook together in her kitchen.\"The word \"me\" refers to.....\r\na, the teacher\r\nc. Mayada\r\nc. the writer\r\nd. Mr. Ruslan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>14. b</p><p>15. a</p><p>16. b</p><p>17. c</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>i&#039;m not sure about number 14, i&#039;m sorry </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-433",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bagaimana Anda mengatakan untuk membandingkan hewan</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>tuh artinya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>adalah hai</p><p> kamu namanya siapa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-the-most-distinguishing-characteristic-of-an-elephant-is-364",
            "question": "6. The most distinguishing characteristic of an    elephant is.....\r\n(A). its clumsiness\r\n(B). its thick legs\r\n(C). its large body\r\n(D). its long nose \r\n\r\nartinya....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. Its long nose</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Yang paling membedakan dari karakteristik gajah adalah D. hidungnya yang panjang :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "soal-choose-the-correct-answer-by-crossing-abc-ord-ana-edi-the-849",
            "question": "SOAL    Choose the correct answer by crossing a,b,c ord!\r\nAna\r\nEdi\r\nThe following conversation is used to answer questions number 1-5\r\n: This park is shadyand the flowers are colorful.I (1).....this park\r\n: I do,too. This is a (2).....park\r\nMono : Look!There are butterflies.\r\n: They are(3) ....\r\n: There are garbage cans too. We can keep this park(4) ..\r\n: I like studying here. The weather is nice. The park is beautiful.\r\nAnd it's a (5).....\r\nPutri\r\nAdi\r\nEni\r\n1. a. want to go\r\nb. hate\r\nc. like\r\nd. feel\r\n2. a. ugly\r\nb. dirty\r\nc. city\r\nd. wonderful\r\n3. a. flyng\r\nb. boring\r\nc. pretty\r\nd. dirty\r\n4. a. dirty\r\nb. clean\r\nc. ugly\r\nd. wonderful\r\n5. a. terrible\r\nb. horrible\r\nc. beautiful\r\nd. pret\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. c. like</p><p>2. d. beautiful</p><p>3. c. pretty</p><p>4. b. clean</p><p>5. d. pretty</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-climax-of-the-strory-true-friends-once-upon-a-time-909",
            "question": "What is the climax of the strory?    True Friends\r\n\r\n Once upon a time, there were two close friends who were walking through the forest together. They knew that anything dangerous can happen any time in the forest. So they promised each other that they would always be together in any case of danger.\r\n\r\n Suddenly, they saw a large bear getting closer toward them. One of them climbed a nearby tree at once. But unfortunately the other one did not know how to climb up the tree. So being led by his common sense, he lay down on the ground breathless and pretended to be a dead man.\r\n\r\n The bear came near the one who was lying on the ground. It smelt in his ears, and slowly left the place because the bears do not want to touch the dead creatures. After that, the friend on the tree came down and asked his friend that was on the ground, \"Friend, what did the bear whisper into your ears?\" The other friend replied, \"Just now the bear advised me not to believe a false friend.\"\r\n\r\n Moral of the Story- A true friend in need is a friend indeed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa klimaks dari cerita tersebut?</p><p></p><p>Teman sejati</p><p></p><p>Alkisah, ada dua orang sahabat yang sedang berjalan bersama di hutan. Mereka tahu bahwa segala sesuatu yang berbahaya dapat terjadi kapan saja di hutan. Jadi mereka berjanji satu sama lain bahwa mereka akan selalu bersama dalam keadaan bahaya apa pun.</p><p></p><p>Tiba-tiba, mereka melihat seekor beruang besar mendekat ke arah mereka. Salah satu dari mereka memanjat pohon terdekat sekaligus. Namun sayangnya yang satunya tidak tahu bagaimana cara memanjat pohon tersebut. Jadi dibimbing oleh akal sehatnya, dia berbaring di tanah dengan terengah-engah dan berpura-pura menjadi orang mati.</p><p></p><p>Beruang itu mendekati orang yang terbaring di tanah. Itu tercium di telinganya, dan perlahan meninggalkan tempat itu karena beruang tidak mau menyentuh makhluk mati. Setelah itu, teman di pohon itu turun dan bertanya kepada temannya yang ada di tanah, \"Teman, apa yang dibisikkan beruang ke telingamu?\" Teman yang lain menjawab, \"Baru saja beruang itu menasihati saya untuk tidak mempercayai teman palsu.\"</p><p></p><p>Moral of the Story- Teman sejati yang membutuhkan adalah teman sejati.</p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ii-uraian-jawablah-dengan-tepat-dan-jelas-1-write-three-hobbie-393",
            "question": "II. URAIAN    Jawablah dengan tepat dan jelas!\r\n1. Write three hobbies\r\n2. Change into Present continuous tense.\r\nMy father read a newspaper now\r\n3. make a short conversation about giving\r\ncompliment\r\n4. Write a short conversation about expression of\r\ncongratulate\r\nSO 5. Write 3 places for vacation\r\n6. Change into English\r\na. Adam sedang duduk di atas kursi\r\nb. Kita tinggal di Medan\r\n7. Write three names of food that you know\r\n8. Write three names of drink that you know\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Writing, Reading, Gaming</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Nomor 6. Adam is sitting on a chair, We Live In Medan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "dimas-do-you-have-favorite-novels-rino-thave-two-favorite-novels-722",
            "question": "Dimas Do you have favorite novels?    Rino Thave two favorite novels. The llounted House\r\nand The Secret Place\r\nDimas What kind of novel are they?\r\nRino The Hounted House is a horror novel, and\r\nThe Secret Place is a detective story\r\nDimas Which one is thicker?\r\nRino \u00b7 The Haunted House has 50 pages, but the\r\nSecret Place has 75 pages,\r\nDimas How much did you buy those novels?\r\nRino : The Haunted House is Rp. 35.000, and The\r\nSecret Place is Rp. 125.000\r\nDimas: I like detective story, too. May I borrow yours\r\nsometimes?\r\nRino Certainly! You may come to my house because\r\nI have more interesting story books to read\r\n26. Who likes detective story?\r\nA Dimas.\r\nC None\r\nB. Rino\r\nD. Dimas and Rino\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Dimas </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena di situ  Dimas bilang \"i like detective story&#039;\"</p><p>maaf kalau salah ya, semangat belajar nya </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ana-arrange-the-words-to-be-good-sentence-me-delicious-gi-473",
            "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627    Arrange the words to be good sentence!\r\nMe - delicious - give - she-food - her\r\n4.\r\n5.\r\nBag is Rp 250.000\r\nWallet is Rp 150.000\r\nBag is..........\r\n..........than wallet ( expensive)\r\nWallet Is...........than bag (cheap)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>\u2022 She give me her delicious food.</p><p>\u2022 Bag is <strong>more </strong><strong>expensive </strong>than wallet.</p><p>\u2022 Wallet is <strong>cheaper </strong>than bag</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p></p><p>Susunlah kata-kata tersebut menjadi kalimat yang baik!</p><p>Saya - enak - beri - dia-makanan - dia</p><p>4.</p><p>5.</p><p>Tas seharga Rp 250.000</p><p>Dompet Rp 150.000</p><p>Tas adalah..........</p><p>..........daripada dompet (mahal)</p><p>Dompet Is...........daripada tas (murah)</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}